8moms.com 2013-08-01

# 8moms: The best mom deals from the best places.

##  Privacy Policy

8moms.com, operated by 8moms, LLC ("8moms"), respects your privacy and values the relationship we have with you. Your visit to this website is subject to this Privacy Policy and its Terms and Conditions.

This Privacy Policy describes the types of personal information we collect at 8moms.com, (the "Site"), how we may use that information and with whom we may share it. Our Privacy Policy also describes the measures we take to protect the security of this information as well as how you may reach us to update your contact information, remove your name from our mailing list or ask us any questions you may have about our use of your personal information. It also explains how you may elect to stop receiving communications about our products and services.

Please note that this Privacy Policy governs only information provided to 8moms.com. If you link to another website from this Site, you are subject to the privacy policy applicable for that website and we suggest that you consult such privacy policy.

##  Information We Collect and How We Use It

You may choose to provide us with personal information when you visit our Site. For example, if you decide to complete an online survey, complete a user registration form or make a purchase, you may be asked to provide certain information such as your contact information (name, email address, mailing address, and telephone number), age group and gender. If you decide to place an order, we will also need to know your billing address, credit card number and expiration date. To protect your personal information, users registering at the Site must also enter a user name/email address and password.

If you would prefer that we not collect any personal information from you, please do not provide us with any such information.

##  Use of Personal Information by 8moms.com

**Marketing Emails**

If you so elect, the information you provide may be used by 8moms.com to create and deliver to you emails such as our newsletters, surveys or other email messages containing product and service information ("Emails"). If you do elect to receive them and later decide that you would no longer like to receive these Emails, see the Deactivate or Change Your Status section below.

**Service Related Communications**

If you have elected to provide us with your contact information, we may provide you with service related announcements by email, or direct mail, concerning the Site or contact you regarding your customer service requests or questions or your order. For example, all registered users will receive a welcoming Email. These types of communications are necessary to serve you, respond to your concerns and to provide the high level of customer service that 8moms.com offers its customers.

**Special Events, Questionnaires and Surveys**

On occasion, 8moms.com may sponsor special events (such as contests, sweepstakes or other offerings), questionnaires and surveys. There may be specific rules applicable to these promotions that explain how any personal information you provide will be processed. We strongly suggest you review any applicable rules before participating. To the extent any special event, questionnaire or survey is not subject to specific rules, the processing of personal information is governed by this Privacy Policy for the purposes set forth herein.

**Technologies That Allow Us to Customize Your Experience on Our Site**

We use various technologies to collect information about your visit to our Site and to enhance and customize your experience on our Site. For example, we may collect the numerical Internet Protocol (IP) address identifying your computer or device which may indicate your geographic location. In some instances, we may use these technologies in combination with the personal information you provide on the Site. These technologies may provide a variety of information such as whether you have visited our Site before. They also may enable you to save your preferences. Each technology is explained below.

**Web Beacons and Tracking Links**

Web beacons (also called clear gifs and pixel tags), tracking links and/or similar technology consist of a few lines of code and are embedded on the pages of our Site. They are often used in combination with cookies and are often not visible to the user of the Site. Web beacons may relay information to third parties such as our service providers and may be used in order to track customer response to certain advertising, to better target interactive advertising and to enhance customer support and usability. If you reject our cookies (see "Cookies" section below), you will prevent Web beacons from relaying this information about you and may limit your use of some of our Site features.

**Cookies**

The Site uses "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of a cookie is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to 8moms.com, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the 8moms.com features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser settings to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the 8moms.com services or web sites you visit.

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use non-identifying information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

##  Information We Share and With Whom We Share It

We will not provide your personal information to third parties for their use in marketing their products or services to you without your consent, except as described below. In addition, we do not sell or otherwise disclose personal information about our Site visitors except as described here.

**8moms Companies**

We may share your personal information with other 8moms affiliates and/or subsidiaries ("8moms Companies"). 8moms Companies will use this information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**Third Parties**

We may retain other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf consistent with this Privacy Policy. Examples include credit card companies, data analysis firms, customer support specialists, email vendors, and web hosting companies. Such third parties may be provided with access to personal information needed to perform their functions but may not use such information other than on our behalf and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

In addition, in some instances, you may be offered the opportunity to consent to the sharing of your information with a third party such as an event or promotion co-sponsor. If you consent, we will share your information with such third party and the information you provide may be used by such third party for their own purposes and in accordance with their own policies.

**Compliance With Law and Fraud Protection**

We may disclose any information we deem necessary, in our sole discretion, to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request. In addition, we may disclose any information when we believe, in our sole discretion, disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss or in connection with suspected or actual illegal activity.

**Minors's Privacy**

8moms.com does not knowingly collect information from minors under the age of 18 years. 8moms.com does not wish to collect information from minors under 18 years old. By registering with 8moms.com, the new member certifies that they are not under the age of 18 years. If a user indicates their age as under 18 then their personally identifiable information will automatically be removed from the 8moms.com database and will not be retained.

##  How We Protect Personal Information

We maintain reasonable safeguards for this Site to protect against unauthorized disclosure, use, alteration or destruction of the personal information you provide on the site. If you have any questions about security at our Site, please [contact us](http://www.8moms.com/pages/contact-us).

##  Updates to Our Privacy Policy

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post the revised policy here. We suggest that you periodically consult this Privacy Policy. Please find the effective date of the Privacy Policy at the top of this page.

##  Deactivate or Change Your Status

8moms.com gives our members the option of deactivating from our service so as not to receive future communications from 8moms.com or any other part of our service, or to change their profile and preferences.

To change your profile and preferences or deactivate your participation in the service, you may:

  * Visit the My Account section of 8moms.com and change your current status.
  * [Contact us](http://www.8moms.com/pages/contact-us) and request to unsubscribe.

Note: It may take up to 48 hours for us to process your request and any e-mail communications within the queue prior to your decision to deactivate will still be sent to you by 8moms.com.

##  Comments

We have taken great measures to ensure that your visit to our Site is an excellent one and that your privacy is constantly respected. If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our privacy practices, please [contact us](http://www.8moms.com/pages/contact-us).

**8moms / Kidville**  
163 East 84th Street  
New York, NY 10028  
Email: [help@8moms.com](mailto:help@8moms.com)  
Phone: 212-772-8435
